formget.com 2019-04-04

# Privacy Policy | FormGet

This Privacy Policy was last modified and published on May 23, 2018, and will take effect on May 25, 2018.

Magnet Brains Software Technology Pvt Ltd. (“we”, “us” or “our”) knows that you care how information about you is used and shared. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by Magnet Brains Software Technology Pvt Ltd. when you use the Magnet Brains Software Technology Pvt Ltd.’s products and services, how the information will be used, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of information. This Privacy Policy applies to our Service, which includes [**www.formget.com**](https://www.formget.com/), and its sub-domains. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources.

#### **Policy summary**

Personal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

**Analytics** : Google Analytics  
**Personal Data** : Cookie and Usage Data  
**Contacting the User** : Contact form  
**Personal Data** : Email and First Name  
**Handling payments** : PayPal  
**Personal Data** : Various types of Data  
**Interaction with external social networks and platforms** : Twitter Tweet button and social widgets  
**Personal Data** : Cookie and Usage Data  
**Registration and authentication** : Direct registration  
**Personal Data** : Email, Password and Username  
**Personal Data** : Email

The Personal Data collected are used to provide the User with services or to sell goods, including payment and possible delivery. The Personal Data collected to complete the payment may concern the credit card, the bank account used for the transfer, or any other means of payment envisaged. The kind of Data collected by this Application depends on the payment system used.

**Contact information**

Magnet Brains Software Technology Pvt Ltd.  
Data Controller and Owner  
Magnet Brains Software Technology Pvt Ltd.

#### [Contact Us](https://www.formget.com/contact-us/)

#### **Types of Data collected**

Among the types of Personal Data that this Application collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: Cookie, Usage Data, Email, First Name, Username and Password. Other Personal Data collected may be described in other sections of this privacy policy or by dedicated explanation text contextually with the Data collection. The Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or collected automatically when using this Application.

Any use of Cookies or of other tracking tools by the Application or by the owners of third party services used by this Application, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify Users and remember their preferences, for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User.

Failure to provide certain Personal Data may make it impossible for this Application to provide its services. The User assumes responsibility for the Personal Data of third parties published or shared through this Application and declares to have the right to communicate or broadcast them, thus relieving the Data Controller of all responsibility.

Mode and place of processing the Data Method of processing The Data Controller process the Data of Users in the proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or unauthorized destruction of the Data.

Access to the Data may be available to Data Processors such as employees involved with the processing or to external parties providing services to the Data Controller, third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communication agencies. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Data Controller at any time. Place The Data is processed at the Data Controller headquarters, unless stated otherwise in the rest of this document. Conservation Time The Data is kept for the time necessary to provide the service requested by the User, or stated by the purposes outlined in this document, and the User can always request the Data Controller for their suspension or removal.

The use of the collected Data The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Application to provide its services, as well as for the following purposes: Analytics, Handling payments, Interaction with external social networks and platforms, Users’ database management, Contacting the User and Registration and authentication.  
The Personal Data used for each purpose is outlined in the specific sections of this document.

Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

Analytics The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.

#### Google Analytics (Google)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

**Personal Data collected** : Cookie and Usage Data.  
**Place of processing** : India – Privacy Policy

Contacting the User Contact form (This Application) By filling in the contact form with their Data, the Users authorizes this Application to use these details to reply to requests for information, quotes or any other kind of request as indicated by the form’s header. Personal Data collected: Email and First Name.

#### **Handling payments**

Payment processing services enable this Application to process payments via PayPal. To ensure greater security, this Application shares only the information necessary to execute the transaction with the financial intermediaries handling the transaction.

These services allow interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of this Application. The interaction and information obtained by this Application are always subject to the User’s privacy settings for each social network. If a service enabling interaction with social networks is installed it may still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.

Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (Twitter)  
The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter Inc.

**Personal Data collected** : Cookie and Usage Data.  
**Place of processing** : India – Privacy Policy

#### **Registration and authentication**

By registering or authenticating, Users allow this Application to identify them and give them access to dedicated services. Depending on what is described below, third parties may provide registration and authentication services. In this case, this Application will be able to access some Data, stored by these third-party services, for registration or identification purposes.

Direct registration (This Application)  
The User registers by filling out the registration form and providing the Personal Data directly to this Application.  
Personal Data collected: Email, Password and Username.

Users’ database management  
These services build user profiles by starting from an email address, a personal name, or other information that the User provides to this Application. This Personal Data is matched with publicly available information about the User (such as social networks’ profiles) and used to build private profiles that the Owner can display and use for improving this Application.

Intercom (Intercom Inc.)  
Intercom is a Users’ database management service provided by Intercom Inc.  
Personal Data collected: Email.  
Place of processing: India – Privacy Policy

#### **Data Transfers outside the EEA**

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. The website aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

  * The **  right to access**, update or to delete the information we have on you. Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.
  * The  **right of rectification**. You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
  * The  **right to object**. You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
  * The  **right of restriction**. You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
  * The  **right to data portability.**  You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
  * The  **right to withdraw consent**. You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where the website relied on your consent to process your personal information.
  * Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.
  * You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).

#### How We Protect Your Information

We care about the integrity and security of your Personal Information and implement appropriate technical and organizational security measures to safeguard your Personal Information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or guarantee that your information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. Your privacy settings may also be affected by changes to the functionality of our distributors, such as social networks. We are not responsible for the functionality or security measures of any third party.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to your email communications from us, at all times.

#### Compromise of Personal Information

In the event that Personal Information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will promptly notify those persons whose Personal Information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

#### **Further information about Personal Data**

Selling goods and Services online  
The Personal Data collected are used to provide the User with services or to sell goods, including payment and possible delivery. The Personal Data collected to complete the payment may concern the credit card, the bank account used for the transfer, or any other means of payment envisaged. The kind of Data collected by this Application depends on the payment system used.

Additional information about Data collection and processing Legal Action  
The User’s Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Data Controller, in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Application or the related services.

#### **Additional Information about User’s Personal Data**

In addition to the information in this privacy policy, this Application may provide the User with contextual information concerning particular services or the collection and processing of Personal Data. System Logs and Maintenance For operation and maintenance purposes, this Application and any third party services may collect files that record interaction with this Application (System Logs) or use for this purpose other Personal Data (such as IP Address). Information not contained in this policy More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Data Controller at any time at its contact information.

#### **The rights of Users**

Users have the right, at any time, to know whether their Personal Data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Data Controller at the contact information set out above.

Changes to this privacy policy The Data Controller reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom.

If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must cease using this Application and can request the Data Controller to erase the Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all Personal Data the Data Controller has about Users.

Information about this privacy policy  
The Data Controller is responsible for this privacy policy, prepared starting from the modules provided by Iubenda and hosted on the Iubenda’s servers.

**Your Choices About Your Information**

**All Users**

  * **Decline to Submit Information** **  – **You may, of course, decline to submit Personal Information through the Service, in which case we may not be able to provide certain services to you.

  * **Update Account Information** – You may update or correct your account information and email preferences at any time by logging in to your account settings page. You can also exercise any of your rights by contacting us directly at enquiry@formget.com

  * **Unsubscribe from emails** – To unsubscribe from a particular newsletter, click the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of that email newsletter. When we send newsletters to subscribers we may allow advertisers or partners to include messages in those newsletters, or we may send dedicated newsletters and marketing messages on behalf of those advertisers or partners. We may disclose your opt-out choices to third parties so that they can honor your preferences in accordance with applicable laws.

  * **Blocking cookies** – Certain browsers may be configured to notify you when you receive cookies or allow you to restrict or disable certain cookies. If you choose to disable cookies, however, that could affect certain features of the Service that use cookies to enhance their functionality.

  * **Disabling local shared objects (e.g., Flash cookies)** – We may use other kinds of local storage that function similarly but are stored in different parts of your computer from ordinary browser cookies, including Flash cookies placed on your device or web browser via the Adobe flash plug-in. Your browser may allow you to disable its HTML5 local storage or delete information contained in its HTML5 local storage.

**EEA Residents.**

If you are located in the EEA, or if otherwise required by applicable law, you also have the following rights in relation to your information:

  * **Inspection and access** : you can request from us a summary and a copy of any Personal Information we hold about you;

  * **Correction/addition/removal** : where you believe your information is inaccurate or incomplete, you are entitled to request us to correct, amend or delete it;

  * **Portability** : you may request that we send you any Personal Information that you have provided to us or ask that we send this information to a third party;

  * **Objection** : you may object to us using your Personal Information where we use it based on our legitimate interests to do so;

  * **Restriction** : you may request that we restrict the processing of your information where you believe it is inaccurate, our processing is unlawful, you believe we no longer need the information or if you have objected to our use of it; and

  * **Automated Decision Making** : where we undertake automated decision making (including profiling), which significantly affects you, you are entitled to object to such decision-making.

You always have the right to lodge a complaint with the relevant supervisory authority for data protection in your jurisdiction.

#### **Sharing Your Personal Information**

We don’t disclose, sell, trade, or rent user’s personal identification data to others. General demographic statistics are not linked to any personal information regarding visitors and users with our trusted affiliates, above outline may be shared with advertisers and business partners.

#### Notification Procedures

It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to you via email notice, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on the Service, as determined by us in our sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We may update its Privacy Policy from time to time, and so you should review this Policy periodically. When we change the policy in a material way, we will update the ‘last modified’ date at the top of this Privacy Policy. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

* * *

#### **Definitions and legal references**

**Personal Data (or Data)**  
Any information regarding a natural person, a legal person, an institution or an association, which is, or can be, identified, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number.

**Usage Data**  
Information collected automatically from this Application (or third party services employed in this Application ), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Application, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server’s answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User’s IT environment.

**User**  
The individual using this Application, which must coincide with or be authorized by the Data Subject, to whom the Personal Data refer.

**Data Subject**  
The legal or natural person to whom the Personal Data refers to.

**Data Processor**  
The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization authorized by the Data Controller to process the Personal Data in compliance with this privacy policy.

**Data Controller (or Application Owner, or Owner)**  
The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization with the right, also jointly with another Data Controller, to make decisions regarding the purposes, and the methods of processing of Personal Data and the means used, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Application. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of this Application.

**This Application**  
The hardware or software tool by which the User Personal Data is collected.

**Cookie**  
A small piece of data stored in the User’s device.

**Legal information**  
This privacy policy is solely about this Application.

* * *

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at enquiry@formget.com
